Onnida Aditapsatit

🖥 +66 6-1407-5018 | 💌 onkwan99@gmail.com | LinkedIn | 🔴 www.onnida.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A quadrilingual professional with highly diversified international experience in B2B business development, sales, strategy, project management, and relationship management in IT, internet, mobile and FinTech industry with a proven track record of sales and project management achievements in both startups and corporate environment. A highly self-motivated allrounder with excellent strategic thinking, problem solving, communication, and negotiation skills; an entrepreneurial spirit with a full passion on mobile internet and technology.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Playbasis (Thailand) Co Ltd **Business Development Director** Bangkok, Thailand

May 2016 - Present

- Leading an international business development and strategy teams dedicated to grow and to expand businesses of gamification and engagement mobile platform in Southeast Asia and international markets; defining and executing the corporate strategy, recruiting and developing the department by ensuring the high performing employees.
- Identifying, qualifying and executing partnerships, developing, closing deals and overseeing key accounts (focusing on financial services and telecommunications industry for mobile payments) in order to accelerate the revenue growth.
 Representing the company in meetings with senior and C-level executives clients, business partners, and investors.

Kimia Solutions

Madrid, Spain

Business Developer for Cost per Installs (Post-MBA Internship)

September – November 2015

• Developed and executed strategic plans for the mobile applications and digital marketing industry while working with social media influencers in a start-up environment.

GT Linkers International Recruitment Consultant (MBA Internship) Madrid, Spain

May – July 2015

• Managed a full consultancy and recruitment process for a fast growing and young start up, with an international scope supporting requirements from the clients on highly-demanding Technology and Finance Professional Services fields.

Covisint (Shanghai) Software Service Company Ltd

Shanghai, China April 2010 - February 2014

- Sales/Project Manager/Customer Support Analyst

 Expanded and grew business in the Thailand/Southeast Asian markets, successfully closing over 100 deals in Thailand and other regions (generated sales valued 890,000 USD in 4 years for new markets)
- Led and managed successfully over 140 EDI (Electronic Data Interchange) project Implementations between Ford and General Motors and all their tier-1 and tier-2 suppliers in Thailand and overseas such as Southeast Asia, India and Russia etc.
 Bridged diverse cultures within company and between clients, as well as managed and developed relationship with new and existing customers.

United Union Parts/Green Filter Company Ltd

Bangkok, Thailand

- **Assistant to Export Manager and President May 2007 July 2008

 **Managed successfully new customers in America, Europe and Middle East; maintained relationships with existing customers and coordinated with suppliers in China, shipping agents and forwarders.
- Handled every aspect of the exporting process such as offering and negotiating quotations, shipping documents etc., while ensuring customer satisfaction through after-sales services and represented the company on commercial events.

The Nation Public Company Ltd

Bangkok, Thailand

Journalist (Summer Internship)

April - May 2006 • Researched, conducted interviews for, and wrote 10 news pieces published in The Nation, the most prestigious English newspaper in Thailand, on human rights and social issues.

EDUCATION AND AWARDS

IE Business School

Madrid, Spain

International MBA (Ranked No. 12 worldwide by the Financial Times in 2016)

April 2014- May 2015

- Awarded Young Talents from Asia Pacific Scholarship
- Focus on General Management, Entrepreneurship, Strategy, Economics, Finance and Marketing
 Winner of Social Entrepreneurship Business Plan of the Year 2014 (Tire Recycling Business)

Yale School of Management, Yale University

New Haven, USA

MBA Short Exchange Program: Global Network for Advanced Management (GNAM)

March 2015

• Been selected to attend Behavioral Economics, Finance and Marketing courses

Bangkok, Thailand

Bachelor of Arts (Honors), Southeast Asian Studies

LANGUAGES | SKILLS

Thammasat University

June 2003-February 2007

Thai (Native) | English, Mandarin (Advanced) | Spanish (Limited professional proficiency) | Korean (Beginner) Salesforces | MS Office | Multilingual Public Presentation | Building Relations | Gamification

MULTI-TALENTS | OTHERS AWARDS & ACHEIVEMENTS

Singer (the Winner of IE Talent Show 2014) | Salsa dancer (Silver Medal in European MBA Tournament 2015 Paris and Top 12 Finalist of World Dance Championship) | Photographer (Finalist of IE Foundation Prizes in photography category) | Model (Published in Vogue Italy, May 2015) | Trilingual MC in English, Mandarin and Thai (Audi R8 LMS Cup 2016) | World traveler and explorer (lived, studied and worked in Thailand, China, USA and Spain; visited 28 cities across Asia, Europe and America.